I have made new screws.
After all, it was small screws here before that were worn so damn.
So now I have turned on hex-screws in stainless steel as I have taken down a bit
So that they can lie along more.
They stood out too much.
Also removed this exhaust valve Pys Valley
Because it sat on the handlebars up here.
But it was so damn ugly with that handle so I have this.
I sat there a cover there instead.
It only worked a 350 so it works.
Then I also got there on the other side when it is finished here.
It looks a little old and thought it was good looking
So it gets a seat here.
I have also made a slightly better oil stick.
With a handle on a bud.
This is how you can see how much oil in.
Before was only a steel wire that they had made a loop on
And stopped into the hole there.
Now I have done so that it is a bit dense there too
And then it gets a little nicer.
There are no original stuff, but the cycle is not original
So that you must not be too stingy.
It is a bicycle to be used.
I got where I had to do the reflector inside with then in
and with me to have 12 volt lamp and then I thought
That then I want some H4.
Now there is no H4 glass here though.
But as I said, this gearbox was also sitting on English motorcycles
So that's probably why it exists then.
So it should be purchased.
So that's probably the only thing left to do on the bike.
Otherwise he goes now.
It is possible to switch and so, but sometimes so hooked up a bit.
Then you get a little on the gear lever and in the end it works.
And the package holder is finished.
Yeah, I had this part but no attachment
So these brackets here.
I have had to do them myself then.
Without there we will see a little what it becomes of it.
I have foot sticks with if anyone wants to go with.
I haven't had to push yet so that's why it has
not become a pillow there.
But it is quickly done and then you just do
a piece of wood with foam rubber and then dress with leather
And then you make a little heel so it remains here.
It fulfills its function now anyway.
And then I replaced the entire electrical system.
Put up the charging lamp and there are high beam lamp.
Then I took such a red lamp.
Then there is a blue diode lamp in there which shows that the high beam is on.
I also found a list.
What you could have for the front screens here.
Now it is a little, a little narrower than the original,
But the screen is also not original so this is similar to the original
Can you say then.
And the handbrake had this bolt where they only took a m6 bolt,
cut a skull and then welded it.
But it was just that that welding flea was so small.
It did not hold for anything the first time
I slowed down here in the garage when I rolled it went off.
I have a damn lucky I didn't ride any motorcycle
For it rattling properly.
So this is now completely reduced so that it really should hold.
Now there is a recessed screw on the inside which is also hard solder.
It will never come off.
Now this is not a thunder good brakes but you have to think about, preferably 5 minutes
Before you start to slow down.
What was it Christer said?
Theoretical brakes!
Yes, there are theoretical brakes.
No it was the back brake I got a little better actually.
It's almost the one you use the most.
Then it was these rubber pads then.
There was someone funny.
I don't know how they made that form, but it didn't fit anything
And then the screws were for long and large skulls.
So I have done that in order now and then the rubber lies
A little bit away.
Because it is against here it lies and scraps a little on the color.
So I made it a little from the thought.
Plus you don't know these screws.
No, now it works.
Has a main switch.
It is easy to turn off that.
And when you turn on the dice, well then the parking is also on.
And then you have it.
There you have whole and half a highlight dipped beam.
Then we'll see.
You get started on the first.
Then you have to flow a little on the carburetor so that you get some gasoline.
Then this is such an engine that would like to kick back.
About so yes.
Don't smell much either.
But it is this gasoline that makes it not those additives
Without them, they become very clean in the exhaust gases.
But then it is not appropriate to stand like this but ...
It's better anyway.
Surprisingly spiteful with to be a 350.
If you look at sales brochures and stuff like that
So there are as many horses in this 350 as it is in Matchless and BSA 500.
So no, he probably hangs with 500 a 1 stump
Fun to drive.
Although you sit a little.
I would have liked to have a lower saddle that went here.
May well try to go on this summer.
Yes, we have to.
Maybe we can take each hi and go to that animal's meeting.
Or go and have a snack somewhere.
Anything.
The most fun thing is to simmer on dirt roads and this one has
the suspension on me all around so it actually goes to
and with suspension in the saddle, which I don't really understand why
They have because they have suspension here.
Plunger I think it's called.
Swaying time when you go, but you don't sit still at some time